Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, resum just the last like minute.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, yeah, so,
so...
Couple of goals we have starting from the
top.
Figure out the anthropic.
Funding channel that works through a
client. So Scribble is an opportunity,
is a mobile app opportunity.
Marty wants us to look at how we could
deepen the Claude feature set or how
Claude is potentially used with this or
come up with ideas for justification for
why this is a good project and why.
Anthropic would want to fund it.
So that's one topic.
Another topic is use this as a catalyst
to try our new methodology we created for
ARC, structure the team,
structure the phases,
and propose that in partnership with
Anthropic and AWS.
just to basically launch that process and
go through it. So we need to...
Look at the documentation we already put
together and try to come up with a
structure.
There's a there's another piece around.
what this,
how this is financially structured,
I don't think that is up for us to decide.
I think we're going to give Marty a
perspective on methodology and team
structure,
and then he is going to come up with what
the actual price point is here.
But you see there's, in this document,
there's a
bunch of information sort of sprinkled
about that. So I think for our discussion,
we can sort of ignore that at the moment.
Okay.
I had Claude generate a discussion topics
just.
from the little information we have,
right? So cloud integration depth is 1.
Economic structure, that's topic two.
We can ignore that for the moment.
Funding, I think that goes into...
After we decide like what the cloud
integration depth looks like,
it's a follow-up conversation,
and same with AWS,
it's a follow-up conversation for...
what their investment looks like.
So then this methodology, team allocation.
and what the scope potentially is for us.
and developing what they've asked for.
I feel like the scope is pretty clear.
In the document,
it seems to be a pretty straightforward
Mm-hmm.
mobile application,
which iOS and Android with,
I think it was React Native.
Yeah.
As the front end and just AWS services
sort of ambiguous in the back end.
So it's a React mobile app, okay.
Yeah.
Um...
It's actually pretty small. I mean,
to be truthful, honest,
I could just feel like,
tell Claude to go knock one out real
quick.
Well, that's what I want to try actually.
So, hold on.
Okay.
I mean, if I have enough detail,
that I was almost like half tempted to do
Ohh.
that before I even started,
just like I could easily knock this out,
like...
Share the documents that I have up.
Okay, so I had I had it created these,
I had Claude create some summary
documents, right?
So this third one is the engagement
approach.
And if we look down here,
this is sort of like the...
their perspective on the phases and how
they play out. So there's, hold on,
where was it?
Yeah, I guess it's this over here.
So anyway,
it's like 12 to 14 weeks to go build this
out. Oh, that's just build.
Phase 2 is build 14 weeks.
I think this needs to be iterated on.
Anyway, a small discovery, like 3...
ish plus months to build and then a whole
beta launch where it's going to be like
rolled out over another quarter and then
another.
Another implementation phase put on top
of that. Hold on, where was that?
Here we go, here's the timeline.
So all the way into the end of the year,
basically.
So we need to find out where the MLP
lands in this,
but it looks like we have three to four
months.
And then there's like,
there's an add-on after that.
Mhm.
And Chrome crashed. Awesome.
Yeah.
I didn't stop sharing, it crashed. Yeah.
Anyway,
Oh, okay, okay.
I gotta figure out what's going on there.
That has to do with my MCPs somehow.
Mm.
I'm doing something anyway.
All right.
Yeah,
I feel like this thing could be jammed
out pretty quick,
so I'm kind of comfortable with...
So Marty's going to want us to be
aggressive.
So they laid out the potential timeline.
He's going to want us to be aggressive in
terms of team to show what we can do in a
short period of time with a minimal team.
I think that's part of what we need to
figure out.
Mm.
Yeah.
Given the size and scope of this,
I feel like it's pretty doable.
Mhm.
Hello.
Okay.
Alright,
so what do you want to go over first?
Which, while we're doing this,
I need to go grab my lunch.
Yeah, go for it.
But I can chat with my headphones on so I
can hear you through my house.
Okay, yeah, sounds good. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I want to go over...
methodology and just revisit it and just
make sure we're not missing something
stupid or we're just including everything.
Mm-hmm.
And then I want to talk about,
or maybe it's not a then, whichever,
another topic is where all.
Does Claude show up?
And...
I don't want to add features for them for
the sake of Claude features,
but I want to have a good business case
for like use of Claude.
So I think it's a multifaceted thing.
It's like, where's Claude in the product?
And then how is Claude used in the
development of the product?
Because there's also like the spend rate
and everything that goes with it.
Yeah.
And then,
and then I think it's a story also of...
Due to that,
there's like claude adoption at the
client over time maybe, right? So.
Mmh.
putting in the pieces so that they can
maintain and manage this for themselves
based with Claude. Something like that.
Okay, I mean,
from the two seconds I gleaned of the app,
it like takes a picture of what you're
scribbling. So I mean,
obviously we'll need a vision model that
can take a look at that.
I wish that would honestly be Claude.
I mean, other than that, I mean,
Claude inside this app is pretty light
outside of its usage.
Pretty the AI stuff.
Yeah.
But we're gonna be using Client a lot,
mainly on the development.
Yeah, I mean,
there's just a few sections where it's
like analyzing and there's requests to an
LLM. So I mean, that would be Claude, but.
I mean, outside of that,
and to your point,
adding new features to News Claude would
be about the only other way.
So I feel like they've already kind of
detailed the usage of AI in this.
But then yeah,
then we're going to use it to do all the
development itself.
as well as do the training and then
Yeah.
We can leave that behind, so then, yeah,
or if they want us to also train their
people, too.
I'm looking at this flow diagram;
it doesn't.
Oh.
It doesn't flow quite like I would expect
on one of the,
we're probably only getting a snapshot of
it.
But they have.
A description or voice text,
so there's also audio processing.
Some gamification.
So behind the scenes there's some
gamification and some tracking and
there's push notifications and all that
kind of stuff.
The voice that can be done on device
pretty much.
The family thing at the bottom right,
I need to read through the specs. Well,
let me let me share.
Yeah, that's what you're saying.
I don't know what that is.
It looks like a gallery of...
stuff that you're sharing or maybe it's
like you're it's auto-generating some see
how it's like there's different things it
looks like they're selecting things and
Yeah.
it's putting them together in a diagram.
You know what I mean?
Like they picked ice cream cone,
Yeah.
a guy on a ship, like there's some...
I don't know if those are drawn or
generated or what is going on there.
That's sort of interesting.
I kind of want to throw this whole thing
at just tell it to build an HTML
prototype of this.
I mean, they would love to see that.
So yeah, back to back to prototyping.
This is to me seems a perfect case for
the prototype is discovery concept.
Mhm.
Where we prototype something out,
like show it to them,
it like is this flow, they react to it.
They say, I love that,
don't like the colors or whatever it is,
right?
And then we just like turn that into
requirements and go.
Yes.
Because yeah,
if you can figure out what questions you
need for me to answer on your side,
I can do that. And then if you want,
I can do the prototype too.
to kind of divide and conquer more.
So...
I don't know that we need to prototype it
in this moment.
What we need to do is tell Marty what our
approach is.
What?
So I think what I'm going to do is,
I don't know, spend an hour,
get some food.
Um...
maybe jam out what I think the team model
is and duration like here's the people,
here's the time,
here's like what discovery looks like.
I'm just going to like.
I'm going to see if Claude can generate
that for us based on our repo.
And just see what it cranks out. I mean,
it kind of already did it in one of those
Mhm.
docs, right?
But I want to see what it cranks out and
see if we can structure it.
And then what I want to do is get your
feedback on that. And then.
Rather than work specifically on those
documents,
I want to work on our arc IDH fin harness
to like figure out how to get it right
for these type of situations.
So that on the next one,
like we come in here and say, oh,
here's this thing, here's the docs,
like let's jam it out. And it's.
It has a better working start,
or at least we have a mobile one to sort
of start with.
Yeah.
That's what I'm thinking.
Maybe create that as like a slash command.
In the arc ideation repos specifically
for what you're looking for,
or a set of slash commands that do
exactly what you're talking about,
and then also remember the advanced tip
of when you're telling it, you know,
give it the overall goal,
and then when you tell it like what you
want it to build,
give like a few examples,
like if you have a page like list,
I want this on there and this on there,
and then be like...
And then I trust you to fill in the rest
of that based on what you know about me
and what we're talking about here.
And then it'll improve and add some extra
Yeah.
stuff, and then we'll have more feedback,
or, you know,
have more to give feedback on.
I.
Exactly. I created last week.
Uh, documents for how to,
for not how to do that,
documents for like different examples.
So here's what a mobile example,
here's a basic web app,
here's like a scale team thing.
And I put that all in like a clickable
HTML because Hemant wanted to show it in.
India, let me go find that,
add that into this because I think
that'll be super helpful.
Also have you review that and see if that
like makes sense to you too.
Because I jammed it out super fast for
No.
him.
Okay.
And then, yeah, other ideas from you,
like qualifying as much as possible, like,
like let's list the potential.
places where cloud shows up and what's
important here.
So you're already saying like multi-model,
like image processing. Now we have audio.
It looks like there's some image
generation maybe in here, right,
where there's multiple things going on.
Wherever else, like I need,
I need to re-dig through these docs and
see what's all in there from a feature
request standpoint, but...
Creating a list of like...
Yeah.
why Claude would be really good for this.
So there's probably a slash command
that's for funding too. Like,
we don't know what the funding looks like
Yeah.
necessarily,
but we can at least like get on it for
like, hey,
here's all the pieces where Claude is in
this product and why it's beneficial.
Mm.
Yeah.
I mean, technically,
all these models can do the same thing,
so it's like,
it's how do we make it clod specific?
I don't know,
we're just using the clod models. I mean,
It doesn't need, I know, I know. Well,
it doesn't need to be...
like, I know it's like, how do you like,
there's no special like sauce that'll
make it really different outside of
Anthropic does train its models to be
more like.
personable versus the, oh,
I got the door closed from the way,
Yeah.
to be more personable versus like opening
eyes is like, it's just a tool.
So as this is more family oriented,
like since we're, you know, using a more,
I don't know, better model, yeah, yeah.
I'm just trying to go up with any kind of
Yeah, yeah.
play to.
Cod.
Well, so.
I mean, you probably already know this.
Like, we don't have to compete with...
Other provider companies like we don't
need to say why Claude over OpenAI.
What we do need to do is say,
these are the services from Claude that
we're using and the expected usage, right?
So this product will cause, or, or,
you know,
use this many potential tokens with this
level of user base, that kind of stuff.
So it's like map, AWS map funding, right?
Like when you go fill out the map funding
and you get funding from AWS,
you're not saying like why it's better
Mm-hmm.
than GCP. You're just basically like,
we're using this compute,
we're using this.
like, you know, these services,
these infrastructure services,
and here's the traffic,
and then they just sort of get an idea of
what the spend is. And then AWS is like,
oh yeah, okay,
we'll give you 50K because we know we're
going to get X back on that if you go
build with us.
So for Claude,
they had that like UX designer thing.
Do you have access to that?
Because I don't.
I think it's built into Cowork,
the one where like you can design UIs.
I did, yeah, it should.
Because I'm wondering if like their
screens,
do they already have designers for them
outside of what we have here?
Because I mean.
We could design them inside of that.
I don't know, I don't know,
but that's a great topic, so cowork.
We updated last week while you were out.
And co-work looks broken for me.
I don't know what's going on. Anyway,
Yeah, it doesn't really, yeah.
I did have that.
I tried it for like a day a couple of
weeks ago when it first came out and I
haven't played with it since yet.
Okay, because yeah, I mean,
that's something we could use it for,
But you should, you should have it.
If you don't have it,
yeah.
let's get it for you, like...
Yeah,
I think he gave me cowork because this
was the guy when I asked for the
integration with 365 and he was like, no,
I won't give you that,
but I will let you have cowork on your
computer.
Oh, man.
I mean, seriously, who puts that in there?
Let you.
It's us.
Thank you, IT, for letting me.
Yeah.
I don't, I don't see it now.
Yeah,
I don't see it like that piece anymore
because yeah,
it used to like you used to be able to
like do it for so many times or
You should absolutely have access.
We probably...
Just need to create a new ticket.
Uh, I need just,
I'm looking at the docs to see where...
Where am I supposed to see Cloud Design?
Ohh, substitute.
Okay, so it's just on the web. You go.
Okay.
Claude, Claude AI dot sorry,
Claude dot AI slash design.
So we should absolutely use this and this
would be great actually for us to learn
how to use design.
Yes, yes.
Yeah.
Our design team is already loving it.
Like they,
I'm hearing awesome stuff about it.
How nice!
Yep.
And then we could take those and then
generate an HTML prototype,
which wouldn't be the full React one,
which is what we want.
And it would be super fast to do while
looking really nice.
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
Um...
All right, we'll add that into our list.
Of cloud services.
Okay, so I'll do a pass.
Um, I'll do a methodology, team structure,
pass, I'll float that by you.
Um...
Yeah,
see if you want to maybe brainstorm
different ideas for clarifying.
Um...
That's a that's a great example.
I want to be careful,
like when I ask Claude to do that in my
little summary,
it just started creating features that
the user didn't ask for and I don't want
that.
Mhm.
Oh.
And so anyway,
I'll send you something in like an hour
because I'm going to get some food too.
Go.
Review that and and.
Let me know if you think it makes sense
if we're being too aggressive or...
Spending too much time.
In.
And then we'll go from there.
Marty wants it right away because he
wants to key up a conversation.
We have another conversation with AWS.
It's like a three-way partner
conversation.
So AWS is a part of this too.
We might get AWS funding. So.
I don't know what that channel looks like
yet.
I'm assuming it's sort of like a map
funding thing.
So this has nothing about bedrock,
but they're going to probably want us to
do that.
And that changes things for us too.
If that's the case. We'll see.
Yeah, I mean,
I think I kind of pointed this out before
where, you know,
as long as we can show the use of Opus on
Bedrock and be like, those tokens were us,
so that should go towards our 10 million
and whatever spend or whatever.
I think that's how we'd have to do it.
I think that's so we can do that just
fine. We can.
We can use API tokens through Bedrock
that are claimed for us and we can show
that spend. I'm not,
also I don't know exactly how that's
Mmh.
going to work in this case because we're
not hosting something,
it's their product on their
infrastructure.
So like those won't be our,
that won't be our spend,
it'll be the client spend on that stuff.
But we should be able to claim it from
however it's tagged, right?
Gregg.
What I'm more concerned about is I don't
want to have to develop on Bedrock
because you actually lose features in
Claude when you do that.
Like it talks to the model,
but then you're using something else.
You know what I mean?
Like you're in Kiro using Opus,
Mhm.
that kind of thing.
You can still use Cloud Code with Bedrock.
You can, you can, but...
So far it looks like you actually you
lose different feature sets that are in
Cloud Code. Like it's paired down.
I need this.
Okay, I don't.
This is a call I was on yesterday where
the team was discussing this.
I've not actually done it myself like
that. So I need to.
I used it on a few projects and didn't
have any issues.
That's why I was surprised because I mean
literally it should just be swapping the
back end and doesn't change your.
Yeah.
Although I could see hitting like their
API tokens with like the caching and
stuff like that. So, okay,
I guess I could see it.
Maybe? I don't know. I...
Yeah.
I mean,
and there's probably more stuff on there.
I actually need to get,
I need to get a handle on this because
we're talking to AWS on Friday and we're
supposed to give a perspective on this
issue, so...
The.
I don't want to falsely claim something
going in there based on that discussion.
Okay.
I mean,
they do optimize a bunch of stuff behind
the scenes and they have prompt caching
and everything else going on,
but I would also assume that's a good
thing.
Not all not a loss in functionality.
Well,
that's so one of the reasons why
Anthropic kicked like all that Clawbot
stuff off was it was making changes at
like the top of like its files and stuff
as it was sending in the prompts,
which was then causing it to not be
cached.
which was then causing a lot more money
churn and stuff like that. And so like,
Interesting.
that's where they also kicked it off
because like it was hitting way too many
times like of a no cash hit when it
should have cash hit.
And so there was just bad optimizations
on that side.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that was the main reason,
or one of the big reasons,
because like that's why they get hit with
like big usages.
That totally makes sense, yeah, yeah.
Um...
Right,
because the the caching requires the
prompt header to be exactly the same
every time, like all that stuff, yeah,
Yep, yep.
yeah.
Yeah.
So...
Okay, all right. I'm going to go crawl up,
do stuff.
Go.
I'll ping you in a bit if you have ideas
or if you have, and you know,
I guess read through this because Marty
wants our collaborative perspective to be
in this.
He doesn't want me to just solo it
because he wants to make sure we get it
right on the first go.
Okay.
Yep.
Cool.
Cool, alright.
All right, thank you, David. All right.
Thank you.